raveaboutit.com.au 2008-12-20

# Local Business Reviews - Rave About It - Privacy Statement

We have a commitment to the protection of online user privacy under the (Australian) Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 (Cth) on 21 December, 2001.

In order to protect your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described below.

This "Privacy Policy" discloses the privacy practices governing our knowing collection, use, and disclosure of information.

All references below referring to "we" or "us" refer to Rave About It.

## User Consent to Privacy Statement

Any person accessing, browsing, or otherwise using the web site located at www.RaveAboutIt.com.au ("The Site"), either manually or via an automated device or program, shall be considered a "Visitor." Further, a Visitor who registers at The Site, downloads, and/or makes purchases of products shall be considered a "User." All Visitors are bound by the terms of this Privacy Statement. Visitors consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of Visitor information pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

## Information Collected

To join the Rave About It site, you are required to submit your name, address, e-mail address ("Personally Identifiable Information"). We store all Personally Identifiable Information. We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors who are not Users. We collect and store Visitors' site referral information, browsing patterns, technical information (e.g., the Visitor's browser version, IP address, and operating system), and other Site use information through the use of "Cookies" ("Information"). (For more information regarding Cookies, see below.) We associate the Information obtained about a User to the User's Personally Identifiable Information.

Use and Transfer of Information and Personally Identifiable Information

We use Information and Personally Identifiable Information as necessary to complete a transaction for you, to better understand the use of The Site and to better tailor The Site to Visitor and User preferences, as well as for customer support purposes. We also may use the name and e-mail address that Users supply to contact Users, as well as to send Users promotional or other materials. To unsubscribe from our mailing list, please follow the directions set forth within the promotional or other materials you receive from us or [contact us](http://www.raveaboutit.com.au/index.php?p=contact_us).

## Information Collected

We will collect general information from you, including the business names submitted, contact name for point person at business, business e-mail, street address, post code, state, phone number, rating regarding a personal experience with the business, and any comments about that experience. In addition, each time you use Rave About It, we will collect general usage information from you including, types of searches, the date your searches are performed and the number of searches you make. This information will help us better understand how Rave About It is being used and will assist us in continuing to improve our services.

Disclosure of Information and Personally Identifiable Information to Third Parties

We may use certain information about you (such as the age bracket that you belong to, or the postcode that you live in) for demographic analysis. This information may be provided to business owners that have a listing on The Site to ensure that they are offering a unique service to you. In addition, we may use this information to ensure that the site is tailored to your needs. We will not otherwise disclose Information or Personally Identifiable Information to third parties, except when required to do so by law.

## Use of Reviews, Ratings and User Names

Rave About It gives you the opportunity to give Reviews and Ratings for local businesses. Your User Name may appear next to your user reviews and ratings as they are posted on The Site. We may also use and disclose your user name, reviews or portions thereof and ratings in any other manner, including in marketing materials.

## Aggregated General Information

In addition, we may share aggregated general information about our Site with our business partners or the general public. For example, we may share information regarding the daily number of unique users to our Site with potential business partners or others. Aggregated data does not contain any information that could be used to contact or identify you. For example, we may count the number of users who have made a review that belong to a particular postcode.

## Cookies

We use a feature of Internet Web browsers called a "Cookie", which is a file that a Visitor's Web browser places on a Visitor's computer's hard drive, to assign an identification code to the computer and to collect and store Information. We associate the Information obtained about a User to the User's Personally Identifiable Information. We do not and cannot use Cookies to retrieve individual Personally Identifiable Information about Visitors from a Visitor's computer. Cookies do not contain any credit card information. The Cookie technology we use cannot obtain information from a Visitor's hard drive or pass on a computer virus.

If you choose to reject the Cookies, some areas of The Site may not function properly or may not be accessible.

## JavaScript

This site makes use of JavaScript to display dynamic content and enhance navigation capability. We assume no liability for possible losses from accessing this site or its content. We have endeavoured to make this site as functional as possible for those users that have JavaScript disabled on their machines.

## Linked Internet Web Sites

The Site provides hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document or to another document altogether, to other web sites not controlled by us. These hyperlinked web sites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

## Children

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through The Site.

## Security

This Site has password security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information and Personally Identifiable Information under our control. We make no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. We shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Statement as a result of a security breach or technical malfunction.

## Sale of Assets

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to the business of Rave About It, we reserve the right to include Information and Personally Identifiable Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

## SPAM

The Site has a strictly Anti-SPAM policy. We have minimised the likelihood of a business receiving SPAM through the use of electronic forms that hide a business's e-mail from potential SPAM search engines.

If in the event an e-mail address is posted by a user or a business on Rave About It, it is not to be inferred as consent by the user or business to receiving unsolicited commercial electronic messages or SPAM.

## Amendments to Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Statement periodically. Use of Information and Personally Identifiable Information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Statement in effect at the time the Information or Personally Identifiable Information is used. Any amendments made to this Privacy Statement will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on The Site.

## Contact Information

If visitors have any questions about our products, services or need to correct their Registration Information, please [contact us](http://www.raveaboutit.com.au/index.php?p=contact_us).

## Submissions

We appreciate and will consider any comments you may have on our Site, the Software Products, service, or ideas you may have on how to improve them. Please [contact us](http://www.raveaboutit.com.au/index.php?p=contact_us) with your feedback. Please note that by doing so, or by otherwise posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting ("Posting") your comments, feedback, concepts, know-how, techniques, software, or ideas ("Submission"), you irrevocably assign free of charge, all worldwide rights, title and interest in all copyrights, patent rights, and all other intellectual property rights in the Submission to Rave About It, its successors and assigns. You agree to cooperate with Rave About It, its successors, and assigns, in perfecting such intellectual property rights. Without limitation, Rave About It, its affiliated companies and its licensees, will be entitled to use your Submission on an unrestricted basis, for any purpose whatsoever, including, to: develop, manufacture and market products incorporating such Submission, to copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate, and reformat your Submission; to publish your name in connection with your Submission; and the unrestricted right to license such rights.

Rave About It does not wish to receive any submission that is confidential or proprietary. You agree not to post or otherwise provide any submission that you consider confidential or proprietary, and any submissions you post will be deemed and treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. In addition, do not post any Submissions that you do not want to assign to Rave About It. No compensation will be paid or is due with respect to the assignment or use of your Submission, as provided herein. Rave About It is under no obligation to post or use any Submission you may provide. By Posting a Submission you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your Submission including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to assign, provide, post, upload, input or submit the Submission.
